Ready?
There's no way.
- Mm-mm.
- This is ridiculous.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's actually impressive.
- You're kidding me.
- Cough it up, baby.
- Okay.
I'm gonna give you five.
I don't know how you do it, man.
- I'm just blessed.
- Hmm.
Thank you for contributing
to my slush funds.
Jesus.
Dude, this place is so disgusting.
Don't trash the bar. It's just bugs.
- You should get an exterminator.
- Yeah, that's above my pay grade.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, geez.
You're such an asshole.
You know, they say when you see one,
there's thousands more in the walls.
- Shut up, Jeffrey.
- Yeah, shut up, Jeffrey.
Why don't you make me?
Make me shut up.
Don't mind me.
Trash coming through.
How you living, Eric?
- Large.
- Expect nothing less.
I'll be right down.
That shirt comes off,
you drink for free.
- No.
- Just saying.
- Oh, yeah?
- That's bar policy.
You get naked, it's free drinks all night.
Isn't that right, Mary?
Damn right.
I don't make the rules.
Come on. Give me a shot.
- Now we're talking. Now we're talking!
- Line 'em up.
Maybe you will see something
by the end of the night.
Don't you tease me.
- Where you going?
- I'm just going to the bathroom, babe.
He seems like a good kid.
He is a good kid.
Wonder how long this one's gonna last.
I'm kidding! Come on, look...
May you both live happily ever after.
Cheers.
Nah, I'm going to wait for my boyfriend.
Your loss.
M'lady.
- Who the fuck are you, man?
- Whoa, whoa. Eric!
- Who the fuck are you?
- Hey! Eric! He's with me.
That's just Jeffrey, man.
You remember him.
Oh, yeah.
- How you doing, brother man?
- Fine.
Thanks.
Good game.
Scored a goal. I'm here!
I was so close.
If you break one more stool, Rosie's gonna
to make you stand while you're here.
Long night?
- Just getting started.
- Yeah?
- Usual?
- Yes, please.
Coming right up.
You know what?
You go buy yourself a drink.
Wow. My man.
And drinks for the progressive couple
over there doing the smooching.
You're a real gentleman, Eric.
Oh, no, man. It's fine.
You don't have to do that.
Yeah. I know I don't have to.
I want to.
Thank you, Eric. We appreciate it.
Thank you.
Welcome.
That shirt better come off now.
Um... to, uh, Eric.
To Eric!
Cheers.
Oh, come on, Eric.
Everybody 21?
Yeah.
What about everybody else?
Yeah, man.
Want me to get them?
No.
Fuck it, you're fine. What do want?
Just beer. Four, please.
Just beer?
All right.
These are twist-off.
Y'all should be able to handle that?
Yeah, man. We can handle it.
You know those kids are underage, right?
Whatever. They're harmless.
Let them have their fun.
Hit me again, please.
Ah! Right, yep. My bad.
Jesus.
I swear, we got more bugs
than people in the bar tonight.
That's fucking gross.
Bugs were fucking on the whiskey.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
There you are.
What's up, brother?
- I'm all right, how are you?
- Good.
Give me a hug, dude.
Enjoying your last days of freedom?
- You know it.
- Good. Good.
What's going on?
You fellas, let me know
if you need anything else.
We're good for now, brother.
- Let's shot some pool!
- Pool!
- Hey, Mary.
- You wanna play?
He's been on a non-stop bender for a week.
He's back on the rig on Monday,
so I think we'll be safe.
Fuck you, Eric!
Hey, Mary!
Mary, come on. They're only kidding.
- Mary, wait.
- Kiss my ass, jerk.
Where you going?
- You're breaking my heart.
- Hey, fellas!
Just be cool, all right?
- It's a family establishment.
- Sorry, Mom!
Fucking animals.
Hey, what'd I just say?
Well...
You're a dick, Eric.
Whatever, babe.
- What happened with Mary?
- He was shoving the cue in her face.
Should we get out of here, maybe? Like...
go?
I'm sorry.
Can you get this man a drink, please?
Yes. Yes, I can.
No. No, no. I don't want... I can't...
- Technically, it's my job.
- I got a deadline. Gotta work. I'm tired.
No, no, no. I have a deadline, so...
Why don't you get wasted and write drunk?
That's what I'd do.
That doesn't sound like the best advice.
Got my ass through college.
Well, yeah, that was college.
You know he went to Tulane.
- Really? That's where I went.
- Yeah?
I think I was there a bit
before your time, sonny.
- When did you graduate?
- The year I dropped out.
Whoa!
Now what, bitch?
Eric, knock it off!
Eric!
Suck my dick, motherfucker.
Hey, Eric! Come on, man.
Someone get the bottle
out of that guy's hand!
Will, call the cops.
Motherfucker.
It's the bartender at Rose's.
We've got another fight breaking out.
Someone's gonna get hurt.
You wanna cut me? You wanna cut me?
Jeffrey, stop! Jeffrey, stop it!
Holy shit.
- Fuck!
- Jeffrey, stop!
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Did you call the cops?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Let's go.
You got him, all right?
You got him.
Dude, what the fuck?
What the fuck? Dude...
You gotta go to the hospital, man.
- You call the cops?
- Of course, I called.
- I shoulda called an ambulance.
- Fucking pussy.
Dude, you got...
Let's go.
Quit milking it, man.
- Let's get outta here.
- You're fine.
Here you go, man.
You all right?
Just fuck off, dude.
Yeah?
All right. Tell that to the cops
when they get here.
Grabbing a bottle in a fight
is chicken shit.
What the hell was that?
You're not a tough guy.
You coulda been hurt.
He coulda killed him, I mean...
- What else was I supposed to do?
- Yeah, okay.
- You did good, kid.
- Fuck.
You did good.
Oh, fuck.
It's probably one of the kids'.
Fucked up that they actually filmed
the whole thing.
Fucking millennials.
Anybody need a drink?
Hey, honey.
Guess who's home?
You feel like waking up?
Mm-mm.
Hmm?
Now stop fucking around.
Good morning, pretty little thing.
Well... Oh...
You're going to make me burn the eggs.
Whose phone is that?
Just some chick. She left it at the bar.
So you brought it home?
Just picked it up...
and forgot to leave it there.
There was bit of a fracas
at the bar last night.
Cool.
Thank you.
How's your paper coming?
I'm nearly there.
I just have to go over it again,
and probably rewrite the ending.
Turn it in to Steve and hope he likes it.
I'm sure he will.
He better. It's a quarter of my grade.
Yeah.
What are you gonna do today?
Don't know.
I don't have any plans.
Probably gonna check on Eric
at some point.
Why?
He's the one in the fight last night.
I thought you said it was a girl.
No, there was a group of college kids,
but when the fight started,
they got spooked and took off.
Eric got cut pretty bad, though.
It was brutal.
Well, that's not shocking.
I should probably go check on him.
What are you doing?
Trying to find out whose phone this is.
Why? Should I not look?
Am I gonna see something
I don't want to see?
No.
Why are you asking?
I don't know.
Why do you know how to unlock it?
From the smudge marks on the screen.
- I'm not lying about the phone, Carrie.
- Okay.
I believe you.
Oh! Fuck!
What?
What's wrong?
Who were you talking to last night?
What do you mean?
You were texting someone.
What is that, Will?
Jesus Christ.
Um...
Don't fuck with it.
Give it to the cops.
Somebody got hurt last night.
Yeah, someone could be fucking
with me, though.
Listen, it's...
Wednesday, so Duane will come in
after his shift. I'll give it to him then.
But what if that girl comes
to get it first?
Just say I don't have it.
Let's let the cops deal with it.
Okay.
Don't worry
your pretty little face about it.
You let your man handle things.
You're gonna make me late.
- Yeah, I am.
- I have to go.
- Mm-mm.
- Will...
you truly smell.
God!
He's only coming in
for that night,
so I said that we would have
dinner with him.
Ugh.
Dinner with your sober uncle?
What is the problem with that?
So he can fucking judge me the whole time.
What?
- Shit!
- God, Will.
Look at these guys.
Fucking here for a higher education,
can't figure out how
to cross a goddamn road.
You know what happens to idiots like that?
- You're gonna tell me.
- They spend four years here.
Four years becoming an economic prisoner.
He should just go work at Rosie's.
Get a real job.
I don't think he's Rosie's material.
No, he should stay here,
and fucking take lessons
from dillholes like that.
Hey, Steve.
Hi, Steve.
I'm gonna go learn from the dillhole.
- Yeah.
- See you later.
Love you.
Sorry I'm late.
How's it going?
Hey, what's up?
- Come have a beer with me.
- Babe, who are you talking to?
Fuck, dude. What time is it?
It's like, 10:00 a.m.
What? Are you still sleeping?
Yeah, I didn't get to bed until sunrise.
Hang up the phone, babe.
You're gonna have a beer with me
or not? I'm pulling up to Rosie's.
No, asshole, I'm not.
I'm gonna go back to sleep.
When did you become such a pussy?
That's so wrong. You know it.
You have one for me,
and I'll see you tonight, okay?
All right.
- Bye.
What the fuck?
How's it hanging there, Rosie?
Oh, right and tight, loose, large.
Pick one.
Anyone come in looking for a cell phone?
Nope. Lost and found?
Yeah.
I heard what happened
with Eric last night.
Oh, yeah.
You should stop serving him
when he's fucked up.
He's always fucked up when he's home.
All right.
I can't leave the bar right now.
Can you go check on him?
Holy shit, Eric.
What is it?
You gotta go to the hospital.
I'm calling an ambulance.
- No, no, no.
- No, fuck that. Dude, your face.
Your face is fucked up!
I can see the inside of your mouth.
It's just swollen. That's all.
I don't know, dude.
I can get a buddy of mine to stitch it up.
A buddy of yours?
Come on, Eric.
You're not in fucking Afghanistan, dude.
Can't go to a hospital.
- They'll ask questions.
- Like what?
You wanna be able to eat food
without it falling out of your face?
What?
Nothing.
Thank your friend for me.
What friend?
The one who's banging your girl.
She's not my girl, dude.
Okay.
I just came to check on you.
I'll let you get your rest.
Hey, don't leave.
Nightmares.
Yeah. All right, man.
I'll stay for a little bit.
Hey, man, you got any more beer?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Uh, $22.50.
Oh, wait.
Don't forget to buy your girlfriend
something pretty.
He'll love it.
Ooh! He looks good in them tights.
Yes, he do.
Next!
I thought you said you didn't want a beer.
I think I meant that I didn't want
to have a beer for breakfast.
Hmm.
Hey, Will.
Hey, Jeffrey.
You get your little project done?
Yeah. Um... turned it in this morning.
Just chilling now.
That's a gold star for you, then, right?
- You hear anything about Eric?
- Yeah, I went and saw him this morning.
His face is all cut to shit.
He's refusing to go to the hospital,
because he thinks he's Rambo.
You want to join us?
No.
No, no. I got to go.
I got a bunch of shit to do.
Just came for some to-go.
See you guys.
Hello?
Carrie?
Hmm.
Monorail, up those stairs!
More of these clowns.
Fuck off.
That's amazing, dude.
Oh, my God.
I literally can't believe this.
Hey, stop goofing around.
Shut up.
- You think we did it right?
- I don't know.
We did exactly what it said in the book.
Oh, my God. Look at the cockroaches.
- Fuck.
- Oh, my God!
Fuck!
Will.
When'd you get home?
Right now?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I thought you were
going to bring that to the police.
I am.
I'll take it today.
What were you looking at?
Who's fucking phone is that?
I told you, it's...
some chick from the bar.
One of the chicks from the bar?
I can't believe you're
still going on about this.
So, what?
All my friends just have to be guys?
Is that the deal?
What about Steve?
You fucking talk about him all the time.
- He's my professor.
- And he obviously wants to fuck you.
You wanna check my phone?
You wanna go through my texts,
see if I sent him any pictures of my tits?
Go on, look at it.
No.
- Go on, check it.
- I don't want to.
I don't want to, because I trust you.
I want to trust you.
But you're being all shady
with some cunt's phone,
and you're acting guilty as shit.
Give it to me.
You don't wanna see it.
You don't wanna see it. It's awful.
Go to the last pictures.
Is that... Is this Garrett?
Is this who you were talking to?
I don't think so.
Those pictures were already on the phone.
- Call him.
- No.
- Then I'll call him.
- No, it's a bad idea. Don't.
I don't want to think about someone
dying like this,
and you'd ignored him.
I ignored him?
He was begging.
That's bullshit.
No one's dead. This is...
It's obviously some fucking nerd
who's into special effects.
Hello?
Garrett?
Ah!
No.
I'm going to call the cops.
Don't.
Listen, don't.
What are you doing?
I'll take it to Duane.
He's a friend. He'll take it seriously.
Do it right now.
Will, do it right now!
Fuck!
Sir, are you okay?
Are you all right?
Want me to call somebody?
- What's wrong with him?
- The fuck is that?
I got your ass right on camera!
I don't see no blood.
- Crazy, man.
- Right?
That's crazy.
Fuck.
Fuck!
There he goes.
- 'Sup, baby? How you doing?
- Just another day. How are you?
Good. Beautiful day out there, right?
It's hotter than sin.
What happened last night?
Why didn't you call us?
I did. Took you guys
an hour and a half to respond.
No, man. I don't mean Fifth District.
I mean us.
I didn't know I could do that.
When last time Rosie's been hit
with an underage sting, huh?
Last time anybody followed up
on a noise complaint?
That's our bar, we protect the place.
Yeah, I know.
- 'Sup, Will?
- Hey, dude.
- How are you?
- Good, man.
Eric all right?
Yeah, he's okay.
- I checked on him this morning.
- Have a seat.
So...
what about the guy that did this?
I don't know.
I've never seen him before in my life.
Kind of figured it was
just something between them.
I tell you what. You see him, you call us.
I want to talk to him,
see how tough this bitch really is.
Yeah, okay.
There was also
these college kids at the bar,
and they left a cell phone there.
I went through it to see whose it was,
and I found some
really fucked up shit in there.
Like what, exactly?
There was a dead guy.
He looked murdered.
- Murdered?
- Yeah.
Where's the phone?
I lost it.
You lost it?
Yeah, on the way here.
But I think it was
those college kids, man.
I think they took it.
They've been following me around
in a black Charger.
I know it sounds crazy,
but my girlfriend saw the pictures, too.
I'm telling you guys the truth.
So, uh, you got a license plate
on this black Charger?
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, I think it started with a six.
A six?
Yeah.
That's it?
Okay, Will.
Look, man, if you, uh...
want to make a statement,
just give us all the details,
and we'll see what we can do.
Sure.
I need to go get the forms.
I hate when people touch
my shit on my desk.
We going to see you tonight?
Yeah, man. I'll be there. Same as usual.
Too much on it, man.
I put too much heat.
About to put heat on your ass.
- 'Sup, bitches.
- How's it going?
- What's up big hair?
- How's the main bitch?
What's shakin', bacon?
Not much.
It's quiet in here tonight.
Yeah, I finally get you all to myself.
Oh, ho, ho.
Speaking of, where's Jeffrey?
Punishing him.
He's being a jealous asshole.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Jealous of who?
None of your business, bartender.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-mm.
I'm just gonna do the one.
I'm trying to take it easy.
Why?
'Cause I don't wanna be wasted.
Then just don't get wasted.
Just do what I do, maintain the buzz.
It's like surfing, only more fun.
I don't think you should be telling me
how to drink.
I need to drink tonight...
and you're here.
So, you just became my backup.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just got some shit on my brain
I don't want on my brain.
I've also got an eight-ball in my pocket.
If you wanna play.
- Try to talk to it.
- Okay.
Just be like, "Hi, what's up?"
Like, whatever, we're so over...
That would've been
impressive if you caught it,
'cause you did extra flips.
That's extra brownie points.
Okay, just like easy, like,
"Hey, how you doing? What's up?"
It's been a while.
- That's too much.
- Yeah, she's playing hard-to-get.
- Try a different one.
- Okay.
- This one's Hubert.
He's much nicer. Try. Ready?
Boom!
- It's that easy. Really.
- It's like, finesse.
Yeah, just like I...
'Sup, yo!
Douglas.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- William.
The fuck does it look like?
I fucking work here.
- You know that, come on.
- It's your shift already?
- What time is it?
- I don't know.
Y'all drunk, huh?
- You're drunk.
- Uh-uh. I'm handsome.
- You drunk.
- We both are drunk.
He's handsome.
I'll take it.
I don't wanna go to sleep yet.
I don't either.
- Don't do that.
- See. These are scheming fingers.
- What are you doing?
- Scheme, scheme....
Let's go to The Fly.
Let's kill this thing.
Okay, there you go.
Co-pilot responsibilities.
Oh, fuck.
So much for cutting back.
Well, I guess there's always tomorrow.
That's the point, Will.
I'm almost 30,
and I'm wasting my life away.
No. I don't think you're wasting it.
I think you're living it.
I don't know.
Listen...
you're drinking tonight
because I asked you to drink,
so that's an exception.
You're basically drinking out of sympathy.
You're like a saint.
Canonized.
Is that the word?
- Yes.
- Deified. No, that makes you a god.
You are a goddess. Let's be honest.
Can a god be a saint?
- Hey.
- Hmm?
You know if you ever need to talk to me
about anything, I'm here for you.
Yeah.
This is so nice.
It is.
There's no people.
I like no people.
God, you smell so good.
Will. Will. Will...
- Will, stop!
- What? What?
What? What's wrong?
You know what's wrong.
What is it? Jeffrey?
Yeah, of course it's Jeffrey.
Come on, Will.
Yeah, but why?
Why? I don't even understand it.
I don't know. Jesus.
I dunno. It's your girlfriend, too.
Yeah, but...
don't worry about her.
- Will, stop.
- Come on.
Will, stop it.
- Stop it!
- Fine.
We should just go.
She doesn't even love me anymore,
you know?
I'm sorry if she doesn't love you anymore.
That's true. I really am sorry.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
I'm on my way. I'll be back in...
Carrie?
Hello?
Hey.
Carrie.
You okay?
Hi.
What time is it?
What is that?
Nothing.
Did you just get home?
Yeah, I... stayed at the bar,
played a couple games of pool.
Let's go to bed.
Hey...
I found your phone on the floor.
Did you send me a picture?
No.
Maybe, I don't know...
I don't know. I feel foggy.
Are you drunk?
No, Will. I'm just really tired.
Come on. Let's go to bed.
Yeah, uh...
I'll meet you in there.
Who the hell are you?
Garrett?
Hey, man. I'm really sorry I didn't help.
I thought you were kidding around.
There was a ritual.
We opened a portal.
Something came and possessed us.
You called it into your home.
Now it sees you are
the perfect vessel for more.
It is in your bedroom right now...
staring at you as you sleep.
Any news from Duane?
I told you,
they'd call if they heard anything.
Do they not care?
Of course they care, Carrie.
What was his reaction
when you showed him the pictures?
I don't know.
He was shocked.
I googled that name...
Garrett.
To see if there are any references
on Nola.com
of someone missing or being hurt,
but I didn't find anything.
Because we don't know
if anything happened to him.
I don't understand
how blasé you are about all this.
You didn't even want to bring it
to the cops in the first place.
God.
Fuck this.
People look so normal on the outside.
What are you talking about?
But on the inside, it's all just...
worms.
For fuck's sake, pipe it down!
Shut up!
Hey, Willard.
Same?
That seat's reserved.
Shut the fuck...
I don't know what to tell you, princess,
but that seat's taken. All right?
Coming right up.
By the way, man, how's Eric?
If one more fucking person
asks me about Eric, I swear to Christ...
Sorry, man.
People have been asking all day.
Any luck with those kids?
The ones with the cell phone?
No, man, sorry. Nothing.
You didn't really give us
much to work with.
Let you know if we find something.
Hey.
Jeffrey.
Where's Alicia?
Hey.
Uh...
Usual?
Just two beers this time.
Okay.
Need anything else, let me know.
Hey, bartender.
Bring me another beer.
I just brought you one, man.
That one's empty.
Doing all right there, Jeffrey?
Hey, I'm good.
- Jeffrey...
- How the fuck are you, bartender?
Let's not do that.
Got started early today, huh?
Bartender, why don't you
bring me another beer?
- You just got yourself cut off, my man.
- Bring me another beer!
Don't take that approach with me, Jeffrey.
- You should get him the fuck outta here.
Pick that shit up, bartender.
You're not a tough guy, Jeffrey!
Quit fucking acting like one!
- Calm down, Will.
- Hey, Alicia! I'll call you later.
- Jeffrey! Calm down!
- You got a problem?
- I thought we were friends!
- Yeah, we are friends.
Get over here so I can give you a hug!
What's the matter with you, prick?
- Stop it!
- Hey, don't talk to him. Talk to me.
I don't want to talk to you.
Hey, was that guy crying?
Yeah, he was,
'cause he's a little fucking bitch.
Will?
Will!
Another beer?
No.
Bourbon, neat.
I thought you had a stroke or something.
- Damn!
- Shit!
Watch the bar!
This is Carrie.
Leave a message and I'll call you back.
Fuck!
They're fucking in here.
Carrie?
Carrie!
Fuck.
Is anyone else in here?
Carrie.
Hey, Carrie.
Carrie, are you okay?
Hey.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck. Jesus Christ.
Hey.
Is there anybody else in here?
Carrie!
Fuck!
Whoa.
Hey! Hey! Are you okay?
Don't touch me!
Shouldn't you be at work?
Yeah.
Why did you come home?
Do you not remember
anything that happened tonight?
I was looking online for something.
I was doing research.
And then I...
I don't know. It's hard to think.
Was there anyone else here tonight?
I think there was.
Oh, my God. I think there was.
Who?
I don't know.
You sent me a picture of him.
No.
I don't even remember
sending you that.
- Will!
- Hey.
Doug.
Yo. What the fuck, man?
Look, are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll be in tomorrow night.
If I still got a job.
Relax. We got you covered.
Just do what you need to do.
Thanks, man.
It's no problem at all.
That's what friends are for.
All right.
Hey, I appreciate it, man.
Bye.
And your boy Eric called down here, man.
Wait, sorry. What'd you say?
I said Eric called down, asking for you.
I told him you went home early.
What did he want?
I don't know. Said something
about giving you a present.
I gave him your number, though.
Probably a booty call.
Look, I don't judge, brother,
but I knew that's what it is.
All right, gotcha.
Hey, Will.
You shouldn't call here.
So, you told him, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't mean to.
Maybe I did. I don't know.
I thought we could go back to normal.
I was stupid.
Is he there now?
Yeah. He's in the other room.
You sure it's a good idea?
Everything's fine.
Look, I can't talk to you right now.
I have to go, okay?
Goodnight, Will.
What the fuck?
We really need to do something about that.
I think we should break up.
I don't think this is working.
Okay.
That's all you got?
"Okay"?
Why are you acting offended?
You're breaking up with me.
I can't believe how calmly
you're taking this whole thing.
I guess you can probably find
a place to crash
while you look for a new apartment, right?
Already? Today?
What did you expect? That we'd cuddle?
Fuck you.
I'm sorry.
It's just this whole thing with the phone,
and the pictures.
It's dangerous.
And I don't want you anywhere around it.
Really?
Are you a hero now?
Come on, Carrie.
Do you hear yourself?
You're scared.
I'm scared, too.
But I would never abandon you to it.
That's not what I'm saying.
Fuck you.
I wasn't mad until just now.
I was disappointed.
I was hurt.
But now, I'm just fucking pissed.
So, if that's what you wanted,
then, you got it.
It's not what I wanted.
You know what I think you want?
Nothing.
Because there's nothing there to satisfy.
You are a mock person.
You're just a body.
You okay?
Fucking Doug say something?
No.
Did something happen?
Nope.
Well, you look like shit.
Have you even showered today?
Hit me again.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Your shift starts soon, anyway.
I'm a grown ass man.
Do I need to worry about you?
Nope.
You really don't, Rosie.
- Oh! I'm sorry!
- Motherfucker!
I can buy you another drink, man.
- I don't want your drink!
- Hey!
No problem, man.
What's gotten into you?
Go home.
Take a shower.
Get your head straight.
What about my shift?
Don't worry about it.
I'll cover you for tonight.
I don't want you to.
Well...
Fuck you, Rosie.
Excuse me?
Fuck me?
Fuck you.
Do you want to keep this job?
Fuck your job.
Hey, it's Alicia. Leave a message.
Alicia, it's me. It's important.
I need you to call me back.
I know you're getting these messages.
Fuck!
Eric.
Christ.
Eric?
Eric, you in here, man?
How you living, man?
Did someone break in here?
What do you want?
Just checking on you, man.
I'm good.
I gotta crash here for a few days.
I gotta stay on your couch...
for a day or two.
No.
I'm up against a wall, man.
No!
I'm gonna clean up
around here a little bit.
It'll be good.
Don't worry about it.
I said you shouldn't call here.
Yeah, but that was last night,
when you were with Jeffrey.
Where are you now? Are you okay?
Will, I'm trying to fix my life, okay?
I need you to stop calling me.
It's not helping.
Wait.
I left Carrie.
I broke up with her this morning.
I'm sorry?
I'm sorry to hear that, Will.
No, that's, that's good news... right?
- I don't know. That's up to you.
- Wait, don't. Alicia...
Will, I'm with Jeffrey.
I love Jeffrey. Do you understand that?
No.
No, I don't understand that at all.
I don't know when
we're coming back to the bar.
Maybe not for a while, okay?
Don't call me back.
If you really care about me,
you cannot call me back.
You can't be in here.
You hear me?
I don't want you here.
Didn't you call me?
No.
Someone called the bar last night
from this number, looking for me.
If it wasn't you, who the fuck was it?
They made me do it.
Those freaks.
Was it the fucking college kids?
Was it?
They told me to give you a present.
Now get the fuck off me!
I'll kill you.
What's the present, Eric?
Are you the wrapping?
You can feel it moving around in there.
Can't you?
Please leave.
Shh.
Most people don't know you.
They don't see the evil
and the ugly in your heart.
You have to be dead first...
or will they rip you open
while you're still alive.
I wonder what would happen if I called it.
Don't do it, please.
Don't do it! Don't do it! Don't do it!
Don't do this.
Fix me.
Make me whole.